

# Jovita Morkūnė Quality Assurance Specialist

- +370 636 58227
- jovita.morkune@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/jovita-morkune/
- Kaunas, Lithuania

#### SUMMARY

I am responsible, diligent, attentive and have good interpersonal skills. I am used to an agile work environment and can quickly adapt to changing business requirements.

Over the past 5 years, I had an opportunity to work with culturally diverse teams, where I was focusing on ensuring a high level of quality in the work my team was doing.

Currently, I'm studying a lot to become a software QA engineer. I would love to join a software company where I could create value by contributing to the quality assurance of interesting software products while also gaining more practical experience.

## EXPERIENCE

## Sourcery Academy for Testers Student

Devbridge

07/2020 - Present

# **Quality Improvement Specialist**

R1 RCM

03/2016 - 02/2020

- Conducted monthly process reviews for each team member per the quality assurance review procedures.
- Ensured the high-quality work of my team specialists.
- Investigated trends, analyzed root causes of rejected claims, and proposed solutions to resolve any concerns.
- · Prepared and leaded training of new and existing staff.
- Improved processes with macro commands to increase productivity and to avoid repetitive errors.
- · Initiated additional projects with other teams, which helped to generate more income for the company.

## **Account Resolution Specialist**

05/2015 - 03/2016

Intermedix

- Identified reasons for denied insurance claims and effectively resolved them by determining a course of action in the revenue cycle management process.
- Made calls to insurance companies when needed.
- Maintained high productivity and work quality results.
- Worked on various projects, collaborated with team members to reach the team goals.

### EDUCATION

International Business 2018

Kaunas University of Technology - Master's degree

Finance 2015

Kaunas University of Technology - Bachelor's degree

## CERTIFICATES

End to End Testing with Cypress: CodeMash (Pluralsight)

04/2020 - Present

JavaScript Essential Training (LinkedIn)

04/2020 - Present

Learning SQL Programming (LinkedIn)				3/2020 - Present
End-to-End JavaScript Testing with Cypress.io (LinkedIn)				3/2020 - Present
Programming Foundations: Software Testing/QA (LinkedIn)				3/2020 - Present
The Web Developer Bootcamp (Udemy)				2/2020 - Present
Global Collaboration Certificate (X-Culture)				2/2017 - Present
SKILLS				
Teamwork	Expert	JavaScript	Beginner	
Quality Assurance	Advanced	HTML/CSS	Beginner	
Analytical Skills	Advanced	MongoDB	Beginner	
Time Management	Advanced	SQL	Beginner	
JIRA	Intermediate	Postman API	Beginner	
Git	Intermediate	Cypress	Beginner	

English Intermediate Lithuanian Native

Russian Basic